A Guide to the Andrew Jackson Montague Papers, 1854-1938
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Andrew Jackson Montague Papers,, 1854-1938
The Library of Virginia
22001
31 cu. ft. and 65 boxes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Elizabeth Hoskins Montague of Richmond, Virginia.
Biographical Information
Andrew Jackson Montague was born 3 October 1862 in Campbell County, Virginia. He graduated from Richmond College in 1882 and from the University of Virginia law school in 1885. Montague entered private practice in Danville, Virginia, then was appointed U.S. attorney for Western Virginia in 1893. Montague served as Virginia's Attorney General from 1898 to 1902 and as Virginia's Governor from 1902 to 1906. Defeated as a senatorial candidate in 1905, Montague served as dean of the Richmond College law school from 1906 to 1909, and practiced law in Richmond, Virginia, from 1909 to 1913. Elected to the U.S. Congress in 1913, Montague served until his death on 24 January 1937 in Urbana, Virginia. He also served in several international organizations and attended several international conferences. Montague married Elizabeth Lyne Hoskins in 1889 and they had three children.
Scope and Content
Andrew Jackson Montague papers, 1854-1938, contain correspondence, financial records, letter books, newspaper clippings, pictures, printed materials, scrapbooks, and speeches chronicling Montague's career as a lawyer, U.S. Attorney for Western Virginia, Attorney General of Virginia, and United States Congressman. Papers highlight Montague's political career and his participation in the Carnegie Endowment for International peace and other organizations and conferences. Some papers concern Montague's activities as a trustee of the Carnegie Institution of Washington and of George Washington University, as well as his teaching career at Richmond College.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I: Letter books, 1887-1901
II: Correspondence, 1854-1938
III: Veterans' Claims, 1918-1936
IV: Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
V: Applications and Recommendations, 1934-1936
VI:Speeches, 1892-1925
VII: Financial Records, 1889-1938
VIII: Miscellany
IX: Pictures
X: Printed Materials, 1842-1937
XI: Scrapbooks
XII: Newspaper Clippings, 1897-1937
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Separated Material
Montague's papers dating to his term as governor can be found in Virginia. Governor (1902-1906: Montague). Executive Papers of Governor Andrew J. Montague, 1902-1906. Accession 45102.
Contents List
- Series I: Letter books, 1887-1901., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 1-2)
  Letter books, 1887-1901, contain Montague's outgoing correspondence while a practicing attorney, U.S. Attorney for Western Virginia, and Attorney General of Virginia.
  Chronological
  - Letter book, 31 August 1887-13 February 1891. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter book, 13 February 1891-21 January 1892. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter book, 2 February 1892-3 April 1895. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter book, 3 April 1895-28 January 1897. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letter book, 30 January 1897-30 November 1901. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- II: Correspondence, 1854-1938., Extent: 37 boxes. (Box 2-38)
  Correspondence, 1854-1938, contains Montague's personal, professional, and political correspondence. Personal correspondence contains letters to and from family and friends. Professional correspondence contains letters contains correspondence regarding legal actions Montague was involved in as a lawyer and U.S. Attorney, as well as his duties as Attorney General. Political correspondence concerns Montague's campaigns for Attorney General, Governor, and Congress and details his struggles as a progressive Democrat against the political machine running Virginia, as well as national politics. Also addresses his duties as Congressman, including legislation. Contains sub-series: A: General Correspondence, 1854-1938; B: U.S. Attorney for Western Virginia, 1893-1896; C: Attorney General, 1897-1902; D: Gubernatorial Campaign, 1900-1901; E: Board of Education, 1900-1901.
  Chronological, then alphabetical
  - A: General Correspondence, 1854-1938., 28 boxes (Box 2-29)
    - Correspondence, 1854-1895. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1896. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, A-B-C. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, D. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, E-F-G. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, H-J-L. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, M. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, P. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, R. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, S. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, T. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, unknown. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1897-1898, V-W. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1899, A. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1899, B. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1899, C. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1899, D. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1899, E. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1899, F. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1899, G. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1899, H. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1899, I-J. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1899, L. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1899, M. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1899, N. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1899, P. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1899, R. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1899, S. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1899, T. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1899, W. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1899, Y. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1900, A. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1900, B. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1900, C. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1900, D-E. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1900, F. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1900, G. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1900, H. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1900, I-J. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1900, K-L. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1900, M. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1900, N-P-Q. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1900, R. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1900, S-T-V. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1900, W. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1901, A. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ba. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Be-Bl. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Bo. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Br-Bu. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ca-Cl. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Co-Cu. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1901, D. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1901, E. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Fa-Fl. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Fo-Fu. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1901, G. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ha. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1901, He-Ho. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Hu-Hy. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1901, I-J. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1901, K. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1901, La. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Le-Ly. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ma-Mc. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Me-Mu. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1901, N-O. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Pa-Pe. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ph-Pu. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Q. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ra-Ri. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Ro-Ry. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Sa-Si. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Sl-So. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1901, St-Sw. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1901, T. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1901, U-V. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Wa-Wh. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1901, Wi-Wy. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1906, A. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Ba. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Be-Bo. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Br-Bu. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Ca-Cl. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Co-Cr. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1906, D. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Dean, Charles R. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1906, E. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1906, F. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1906, G. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1906, H. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1906, J. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1906, K. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1906, L. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Ma-Mc. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Me-Mo. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Montague. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1906, N. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1906, O. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1906, P. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1906-1907, Pan-American Conference. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1906, R. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Sa-Sh. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Si-Su. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1906, t. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Unknown. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1906, V. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Wa-Wh. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1906, Wi-Wo. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1906, y. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1907, A. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Ba-Bo. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Br-Bu. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Ca-Cl. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Co-Cu. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Da-De. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Di-Du. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1907, E-F. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1907, G. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Ha-Hi. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Ho-Hu. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1907, I-J-K. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1907, La-Le. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Li-Lu. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Ma-Mc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1907, McKean. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Me-Mo. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Montague. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1907, N-O. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Pa-Pe. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Ph-Pu. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Q. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1907, R. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Sa-Sh. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Si-Su. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1907, T. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1907, U-V (including unknown). (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Wa-Wh. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Wi-Wo. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1907, Y. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1908, A. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Ba-Bl. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Bo-By. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Ca-Ch. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Cl-Cu. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Da-Di. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Do-Du. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1908, E. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1908, F. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1908, G. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Ha. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1908, He-Hu. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1908, I-J. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1908, K. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1908, L. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Ma-Mi. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Mo-My. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1908, N-O. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1908, P. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Q. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1908, R. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Sa-Sh. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Si-Sy. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1908, T. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1908, U-V. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Wa-Wh. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Wi-Wy. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1908, Y. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1909, A. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1909, Ba-Bl. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1909, Bo-By. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1909, C. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1909, D. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1909, E-F. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1909, G. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1909, H. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1909, I-J. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1909, K. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1909, L. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1909, M. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1909, Montague. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1909, N-O. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1909, P-Q. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1909, R. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1909, Sa-Se. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1909, Sh-St. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1909, T-U-V. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1909, W. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1910, A. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Ba-Bi. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Bl-By. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Ca. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Ch-Cu. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1910, D. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1910, E-F. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1910, G. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1910, H. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1910, I-J. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1910, K. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1910, L. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1910, M. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Montague. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1910, N-O. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Pa-Pe. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Ph-Q. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1910, R. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Sa-Si. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Sm-St. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1910, T-U-V. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1910, W. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1910, Y. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1911, A. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Ba-Bl. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Bo-By. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Ca. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Ch-Cu. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1911, D. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1911, E-F. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1911, G. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1911, H. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1911, I-J. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1911, K. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1911, L. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Ma-Mi. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Mo. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1911, N-O. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1911, P-Q. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1911, R. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Sa-Sl. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Sm-Sw. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1911, T-V. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1911, W. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1911, Y-Z. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1912, A. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Ba-Bo. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Br-By. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Ca-Ce. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Ch-Cu. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1912, D. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1912, E. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1912, F. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1912, G. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Ha-Hi. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Ho-Hu. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1912, I-J. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1912, K. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1912, La-Le. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Li-Ly. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Ma-Me. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Mi-Mu. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1912, N. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1912, O. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1912, P-Q. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1912, R. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Sa-Sc. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Se-Sp. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1912, St-Sw. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1912, T. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1912, U-V. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Wa-Wh. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Wi-Wy. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1912, Y. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, A. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Armor factory/Richmnod. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, B. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, C. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, D. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, E. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, F. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, G. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, H. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Hunt. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, I-J. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, K-L. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, M. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Montague. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Montague, Robert Lynch. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, N-O. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, P. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Q. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, R. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Sa-Si. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, Smith-Smithy. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, So-Sw. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, T. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, U. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, V. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1915, W. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, A. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, B. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, C. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, D-F. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, Dickinson, A. B. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, G-H-I. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, K-L. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, M. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, N-P-Q. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, R-S. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1917, RF&P Railroad Relief Bill. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, T. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1917, Trading with the Enemy Act. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, U-V. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918, Universal Military Training. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1917, W. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, A. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, B. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, C. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, D-E-F. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, G-H-I. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, J-K-L. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, M. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, Montague. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, N-O-P. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, R-S. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, T. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, U-V. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1926, W. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, A. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Ba-Bi. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1928, Bacharach Bill. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Bl-Br. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Bu-By. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, C. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, D-E-F. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, G-H-I. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, J-K. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, L. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Ma. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Mc. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Me-Mi. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Mo-Mu. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Montague. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Montague, Roberty Lynch. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, N-O-P. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, R. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Sa-Sh. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Sl-Sw. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, T-V. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, Wa. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, We-Y. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1929, A. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1929, Ba-Bl. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1929, Bo-By. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1929, Ca-Ch. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1929, Cl-Cu. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1929, Copyright Act. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1929, D-E-F. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1929, Flanagan Clippings. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1929, G-H-I. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1929, J-K-L. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1929, M. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1929, N-O-P. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1929, R-S. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1929, T-V-W-Y. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, A. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, Ba-Bo. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, Br-Bu. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, Ca-Ch. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, Cl-Cr. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, Cramton Bill. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, D-E-F. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, G-H-I. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, Interparliamentary Union. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932, J-K-L. (Box 23, Folder 10)